<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?>
<sst xmlns="http://schemas.openxmlformats.org/spreadsheetml/2006/main" count="1155" uniqueCount="517">
<si>
<t>The Process Aspect of Project Success: An Empirical Test</t>
</si>
<si>
<t>International Journal of Information Technology Project Management (IJITPM)</t>
</si>
<si>
<t>Durmic, Nermina</t>
</si>
<si>
<t>Evaluation of Determinants of Software Quality in Offshored Software Projects: Empirical Evidences From India</t>
</si>
<si>
<t>Kannabiran, Ganesan; Sankaran, K.</t>
</si>
<si>
<t>Investigating the Relationship between Activities of Project Management Offices and Project Stakeholder Satisfaction</t>
</si>
<si>
<t>Güngör, Dilek Özdemir; Gözlü, S&amp;#305;tk&amp;#305;</t>
</si>
<si>
<t>Patterns of Social Intelligence and Leadership Style for Effective Virtual Project Management</t>
</si>
<si>
<t>Nauman, Shazia</t>
</si>
<si>
<t>Building Resilience in Large High-Technology Projects: Front End Conditioning for Success</t>
</si>
<si>
<t>Crosby, Phil</t>
</si>
<si>
<t>Information Technology Project Performance: The Impact of Critical Success Factors</t>
</si>
<si>
<t>Lind, Mary R.; Culler, Evetta</t>
</si>
<si>
<t>Understanding the Factors Affecting the Adoption of Project Portfolio Management Software Through Topic Modeling of Online Software Reviews</t>
</si>
<si>
<t>Daradkeh, Mohammad</t>
</si>
<si>
<t>How Can Agile Methodologies Be Used to Enhance the Success of Information Technology Projects?</t>
</si>
<si>
<t>Truong, Dothang; Jitbaipoon, Thawatchai</t>
</si>
<si>
<t>Probabilistic Method for Managing Common Risks in Software Project Scheduling Based on Program Evaluation Review Technique</t>
</si>
<si>
<t>Huynh, Quyet-Thang; Nguyen, Ngoc-Tuan</t>
</si>
<si>
<t>Knowledge of IT Project Success and Failure Factors: Towards an Integration into the SDLC</t>
</si>
<si>
<t>Al-Ahmad, Walid</t>
</si>
<si>
<t>Comparing development approaches and reuse strategies: An empirical evaluation of developer views from the aerospace industry</t>
</si>
<si>
<t>Information and Software Technology</t>
</si>
<si>
<t>Varnell-Sarjeant, Julia; Amschler Andrews, Anneliese; Lucente, Joe; Stefik, Andreas</t>
</si>
<si>
<t>A systematic literature review on software measurement programs</t>
</si>
<si>
<t>Tahir, Touseef; Rasool, Ghulam; Gencel, Cigdem</t>
</si>
<si>
<t>The longitudinal, chronological case study research strategy: A definition, and an example from IBM Hursley Park</t>
</si>
<si>
<t>Rainer, Austen</t>
</si>
<si>
<t>Time pressure in software engineering: A systematic review</t>
</si>
<si>
<t>Kuutila, Miikka; Mäntylä, Mika; Farooq, Umar; Claes, Maëlick</t>
</si>
<si>
<t>A model of requirements engineering in software startups</t>
</si>
<si>
<t>Melegati, Jorge; Goldman, Alfredo; Kon, Fabio; Wang, Xiaofeng</t>
</si>
<si>
<t>State of the practice: An exploratory analysis of schedule estimation and software project success prediction</t>
</si>
<si>
<t>Verner, J. M.; Evanco, W. M.; Cerpa, N.</t>
</si>
<si>
<t>Evaluating logistic regression models to estimate software project outcomes</t>
</si>
<si>
<t>Cerpa, Narciso; Bardeen, Matthew; Kitchenham, Barbara; Verner, June</t>
</si>
<si>
<t>Case study: factors for early prediction of software development success</t>
</si>
<si>
<t>Drew Procaccino, J; Verner, June M; Overmyer, Scott P; Darter, Marvin E</t>
</si>
<si>
<t>Determinants of software quality: A survey of information systems project managers</t>
</si>
<si>
<t>Gorla, Narasimhaiah; Lin, Shang-Che</t>
</si>
<si>
<t>Formal model for assigning human resources to teams in software projects</t>
</si>
<si>
<t>André, Margarita; Baldoquín, María G.; Acuña, Silvia T.</t>
</si>
<si>
<t>Understanding the relationship of conflict and success in software development projects</t>
</si>
<si>
<t>Basirati, Mohammad R.; Otasevic, Marko; Rajavi, Koushyar; Böhm, Markus; Krcmar, Helmut</t>
</si>
<si>
<t>A survey on the characteristics of projects with success in delivering client benefits</t>
</si>
<si>
<t>Jørgensen, Magne</t>
</si>
<si>
<t>Architecture of Sysperanto: A Model-Based Ontology of the IS Field</t>
</si>
<si>
<t>Communications of the Association for Information Systems</t>
</si>
<si>
<t>Alter, Steven.</t>
</si>
<si>
<t>How Does Enterprise Architecture Add Value to Organisations?</t>
</si>
<si>
<t>Tamm, Toomas; Seddon, Peter B; Shanks, Graeme; Reynolds, Peter.</t>
</si>
<si>
<t>The Work System Method for Understanding Information Systems and Information Systems Research</t>
</si>
<si>
<t>An Updated ERP Systems Annotated Bibliography: 2001-2005</t>
</si>
<si>
<t>Esteves, Jose; Bohorquez, Victor.</t>
</si>
<si>
<t>Customer Satisfaction in IS Projects: Assessing the Role of Process and Product Performance</t>
</si>
<si>
<t>Basten, Dirk; Pankratz, Oleg.</t>
</si>
<si>
<t>Determinants of Information Systems and Information Technology Project Team Success: A Literature Review and a Conceptual Model</t>
</si>
<si>
<t>Fanta, Tesgera Jetu; Riedl, René.</t>
</si>
<si>
<t>Institutional entrepreneurship and infrastructure public-private partnership (PPP): Unpacking the role of social actors in implementing PPP projects</t>
</si>
<si>
<t>International Journal of Project Management</t>
</si>
<si>
<t>Biygautane, Mhamed; Neesham, Cristina; Al-Yahya, Khalid Othman</t>
</si>
<si>
<t>Errors, lies and misunderstandings: Systematic review on behavioural decision making in projects</t>
</si>
<si>
<t>Stingl, Verena; Geraldi, Joana</t>
</si>
<si>
<t>The process of social alignment and misalignment within a complex IT project</t>
</si>
<si>
<t>Gilchrist, Alicia; Burton-Jones, Andrew; Green, Peter</t>
</si>
<si>
<t>Toward gendered projects in international development: Paradoxes, resistance and convergent approaches</t>
</si>
<si>
<t>Brière, Sophie; Auclair, Isabelle</t>
</si>
<si>
<t>Towards a better modelling and assessment of construction risk: Insights from a literature review</t>
</si>
<si>
<t>Taroun, Abdulmaten</t>
</si>
<si>
<t>Improving project management performance of large contractors using benchmarking approach</t>
</si>
<si>
<t>Luu, Van Truong; Kim, Soo-Yong; Huynh, Tuan-Anh</t>
</si>
<si>
<t>How to assess stakeholders' influence in project management? A proposal based on the Analytic Network Process</t>
</si>
<si>
<t>Aragonés-Beltrán, Pablo; García-Melón, Mónica; Montesinos-Valera, Jesús</t>
</si>
<si>
<t>The effectiveness in managing a group of multiple projects: Factors of influence and measurement criteria</t>
</si>
<si>
<t>Patanakul, Peerasit; Milosevic, Dragan</t>
</si>
<si>
<t>Evaluating the level of stakeholder involvement during the project planning processes of building projects</t>
</si>
<si>
<t>Heravi, Amirhossein; Coffey, Vaughan; Trigunarsyah, Bambang</t>
</si>
<si>
<t>The relative importance of tender evaluation and contractor selection criteria</t>
</si>
<si>
<t>Watt, D. J.; Kayis, B.; Willey, K.</t>
</si>
<si>
<t>Conceptualising the lessons-learned process in project management: Towards a triple-loop learning framework</t>
</si>
<si>
<t>McClory, Sue; Read, Martin; Labib, Ashraf</t>
</si>
<si>
<t>Theory and practice of project management in construction</t>
</si>
<si>
<t>Knoepfel, H</t>
</si>
<si>
<t>What is project governance and what are its origins?</t>
</si>
<si>
<t>Ahola, Tuomas; Ruuska, Inkeri; Artto, Karlos; Kujala, Jaakko</t>
</si>
<si>
<t>The development and delivery of an industry led project management professional development programme: A case study in project management education and success management</t>
</si>
<si>
<t>Alam, Mehmood; Gale, Andrew; Brown, Mike; Kidd, Callum</t>
</si>
<si>
<t>Key project management practices affecting Singaporean firms’ project performance in China</t>
</si>
<si>
<t>Ling, Florence Yean Yng; Low, Sui Pheng; Wang, Shou Qing; Lim, Hwee Hua</t>
</si>
<si>
<t>Factors affecting cost performance: evidence from Indian construction projects</t>
</si>
<si>
<t>Iyer, K. C.; Jha, K. N.</t>
</si>
<si>
<t>Standardized project management may increase development projects success</t>
</si>
<si>
<t>Milosevic, Dragan; Patanakul, Peerasit</t>
</si>
<si>
<t>HRM in project groups: The effect of project duration on team development effectiveness</t>
</si>
<si>
<t>Zwikael, Ofer; Unger-Aviram, Esther</t>
</si>
<si>
<t>A case study approach for developing a project performance evaluation system</t>
</si>
<si>
<t>Cao, Qing; Hoffman, James J.</t>
</si>
<si>
<t>Applying a Risk Management Process (RMP) to manage cost risk for an EHV transmission line project</t>
</si>
<si>
<t>Tummala, V M Rao; Burchett, John F</t>
</si>
<si>
<t>Rethinking dichotomization: A critical perspective on the use of “hard” and “soft” in project management research</t>
</si>
<si>
<t>Karrbom Gustavsson, Tina; Hallin, Anette</t>
</si>
<si>
<t>Modeling construction time in Spanish building projects</t>
</si>
<si>
<t>Guerrero, Miguel A.; Villacampa, Yolanda; Montoyo, Andrés</t>
</si>
<si>
<t>Project planning practices based on enterprise resource planning systems in small and medium enterprises — A case study from the Republic of Macedonia</t>
</si>
<si>
<t>Tasevska, Frosina; Damij, Talib; Damij, Nadja</t>
</si>
<si>
<t>MPCS: Multidimensional Project Control System</t>
</si>
<si>
<t>Rozenes, Shai; Vitner, Gad; Spraggett, Stuart</t>
</si>
<si>
<t>Structural equation model for assessing impacts of contractor's performance on project success</t>
</si>
<si>
<t>Doloi, Hemanta; Iyer, K. C.; Sawhney, Anil</t>
</si>
<si>
<t>A study of the impact of project classification on project risk indicators</t>
</si>
<si>
<t>Yim, Rachel; Castaneda, Jason; Doolen, Toni; Tumer, Irem; Malak, Richard</t>
</si>
<si>
<t>Project management in the live entertainment industry: what is different?</t>
</si>
<si>
<t>Hartman, Francis; Ashrafi, Rafi; Jergeas, George</t>
</si>
<si>
<t>Critical COMs of success in large-scale construction projects: Evidence from Thailand construction industry</t>
</si>
<si>
<t>Toor, Shamas-ur-Rehman; Ogunlana, Stephen O.</t>
</si>
<si>
<t>Rating defence major project success: The role of personal attributes and stakeholder relationships</t>
</si>
<si>
<t>Mazur, Alicia; Pisarski, Anne; Chang, Artemis; Ashkanasy, Neal M.</t>
</si>
<si>
<t>The influence of business managers' IT competence on IT project success</t>
</si>
<si>
<t>Engelbrecht, Jacus; Johnston, Kevin Allan; Hooper, Val</t>
</si>
<si>
<t>Manager emotional intelligence and project success: The mediating role of job satisfaction and trust</t>
</si>
<si>
<t>Rezvani, Azadeh; Chang, Artemis; Wiewiora, Anna; Ashkanasy, Neal M.; Jordan, Peter J.; Zolin, Roxanne</t>
</si>
<si>
<t>Linking entrepreneurial orientation to project success</t>
</si>
<si>
<t>Martens, Cristina Dai Prá; Machado, Franklin Jean; Martens, Mauro Luiz; Silva, Filipe Quevedo Pires de Oliveira e; Freitas, Henrique Mello Rodrigues de</t>
</si>
<si>
<t>Critical success factors for World Bank projects: An empirical investigation</t>
</si>
<si>
<t>Ika, Lavagnon A.; Diallo, Amadou; Thuillier, Denis</t>
</si>
<si>
<t>Towards a contingent approach of customer involvement in defence projects: An exploratory study</t>
</si>
<si>
<t>Peled, Michael; Dvir, Dov</t>
</si>
<si>
<t>Systems Engineering to improve the governance in complex project environments</t>
</si>
<si>
<t>Locatelli, Giorgio; Mancini, Mauro; Romano, Erika</t>
</si>
<si>
<t>Selecting the appropriate project delivery method using AHP</t>
</si>
<si>
<t>Al Khalil, Mohammed I</t>
</si>
<si>
<t>The impact of contractors’ attributes on construction project success: A post construction evaluation</t>
</si>
<si>
<t>Alzahrani, Jaman I.; Emsley, Margaret W.</t>
</si>
<si>
<t>Success conditions for international development capacity building projects</t>
</si>
<si>
<t>Ika, Lavagnon A.; Donnelly, Jennifer</t>
</si>
<si>
<t>The integration of project management and organizational change management is now a necessity</t>
</si>
<si>
<t>Hornstein, Henry A.</t>
</si>
<si>
<t>Different stakeholder groups and their perceptions of project success</t>
</si>
<si>
<t>Davis, Kate</t>
</si>
<si>
<t>Software development project success and failure from the supplier's perspective: A systematic literature review</t>
</si>
<si>
<t>Savolainen, Paula; Ahonen, Jarmo J.; Richardson, Ita</t>
</si>
<si>
<t>How to go global: A transformative process model for the transition towards globally distributed software development projects</t>
</si>
<si>
<t>Drechsler, Andreas; Breth, Sophia</t>
</si>
<si>
<t>Cultural Patterns Influencing Project Team Behavior in Sub-Saharan Africa: A Case Study in Ethiopia</t>
</si>
<si>
<t>Project Management Journal</t>
</si>
<si>
<t>Jetu, Fanta Tesgera; Riedl, René; Roithmayr, Friedrich</t>
</si>
<si>
<t>Identifying and Acting on Early Warning Signs in Complex Projects</t>
</si>
<si>
<t>Williams, Terry; Klakegg, Ole Jonny; Walker, Derek H. T.; Andersen, Bjørn; Magnussen, Ole Morten</t>
</si>
<si>
<t>The Three Secrets of Megaproject Success: Clear Strategic Vision, Total Alignment, and Adapting to Complexity</t>
</si>
<si>
<t>Shenhar, Aaron; Holzmann, Vered</t>
</si>
<si>
<t>The Dynamics of Collaboration in Multipartner Projects</t>
</si>
<si>
<t>Dietrich, Perttu; Eskerod, Pernille; Dalcher, Darren; Sandhawalia, Birinder</t>
</si>
<si>
<t>New Insights into Project Management Research: A Natural Sciences Comparative</t>
</si>
<si>
<t>Joslin, Robert; Müller, Ralf</t>
</si>
<si>
<t>A Project Management Research Framework Integrating Multiple Theoretical Perspectives and Influencing Factors</t>
</si>
<si>
<t>Hanisch, Bastian; Wald, Andreas</t>
</si>
<si>
<t>The Influence of Project Commitment and Team Commitment on the Relationship between Trust and Knowledge Sharing in Project Teams</t>
</si>
<si>
<t>Buvik, Marte Pettersen; Tvedt, Sturle Danielsen</t>
</si>
<si>
<t>Leadership in Temporary Organizations: A Review of Leadership Theories and a Research Agenda</t>
</si>
<si>
<t>Tyssen, Ana K.; Wald, Andreas; Spieth, Patrick</t>
</si>
<si>
<t>Developing a Cost Overrun Predictive Model for Complex Systems Development Projects</t>
</si>
<si>
<t>Adoko, Moses T.; Mazzuchi, Thomas A.; Sarkani, Shahram</t>
</si>
<si>
<t>Identifying Success Factors in Construction Projects: A Case Study</t>
</si>
<si>
<t>Williams, Terry</t>
</si>
<si>
<t>Effort of EAI Projects: A Repertory Grid Investigation of Influencing Factors</t>
</si>
<si>
<t>Wagner, Holger; Pankratz, Oleg; Mellis, Werner; Basten, Dirk</t>
</si>
<si>
<t>Closing the Stakeholder Expectation Gap: Managing Customer Expectations toward the Process of Developing Information Systems</t>
</si>
<si>
<t>Basten, Dirk; Stavrou, Georgios; Pankratz, Oleg</t>
</si>
<si>
<t>Understanding the Value of Project Management: First Steps on an International Investigation in Search of Value</t>
</si>
<si>
<t>Thomas, Janice; Mullaly, Mark</t>
</si>
<si>
<t>Managing the Institutional Context for Projects</t>
</si>
<si>
<t>Morris, Peter W. G.; Geraldi, Joana</t>
</si>
<si>
<t>How Standard Are Standards: An Examination of Language Emphasis in Project Management Standards</t>
</si>
<si>
<t>Crawford, Lynn; Pollack, Julien; England, David</t>
</si>
<si>
<t>The Influence of Critical Success Factors on Value for Money Viability Analysis in Public–Private Partnership Projects</t>
</si>
<si>
<t>Almarri, Khalid; Boussabaine, Halim</t>
</si>
<si>
<t>A Bibliometric View on the Use of Contingency Theory in Project Management Research</t>
</si>
<si>
<t>The Logical Framework Approach-Millennium</t>
</si>
<si>
<t>Couillard, Jean; Garon, Serge; Riznic, Jovica</t>
</si>
<si>
<t>Lagomizing, Organic Integration, and Systems Emergency Wards: Innovative Practices in Managing Complex Systems Development Projects</t>
</si>
<si>
<t>Berggren, Christian; Järkvik, Jack; Söderlund, Jonas</t>
</si>
<si>
<t>Project Management Systems: Moving Project Management from an Operational to a Strategic Discipline</t>
</si>
<si>
<t>Cooke-Davies, Terence J.; Crawford, Lynn H.; Lechler, Thomas G.</t>
</si>
<si>
<t>Exploring the Relationship between Rework Projects and Risk Indicators</t>
</si>
<si>
<t>Yim, Rachel L.; Castaneda, Jason M.; Doolen, Toni L.; Tumer, Irem Y.; Malak, Richard</t>
</si>
<si>
<t>Inter-Team Coordination Patterns and Outcomes in Multi-Team Projects</t>
</si>
<si>
<t>Dietrich, Perttu; Kujala, Jaakko; Artto, Karlos</t>
</si>
<si>
<t>Project Management Training Curricula at South African Public Universities: Is the Balanced Demand of the Profession Sufficiently Accommodated?</t>
</si>
<si>
<t>Louw, Thelma; Rwelamila, P. D.</t>
</si>
<si>
<t>Discriminating Contexts and Project Management Best Practices on Innovative and Noninnovative Projects</t>
</si>
<si>
<t>Besner, Claude; Hobbs, Brian</t>
</si>
<si>
<t>Project Stakeholder Management—Past and Present</t>
</si>
<si>
<t>Eskerod, Pernille; Huemann, Martina; Savage, Grant</t>
</si>
<si>
<t>The Project Manager/Functional Manager Partnership</t>
</si>
<si>
<t>Pitagorsky, George</t>
</si>
<si>
<t>The Sales Process of Information Systems: Implications for Project Execution and Business Benefits</t>
</si>
<si>
<t>Fulford, Richard</t>
</si>
<si>
<t>The Perceived Value and Potential Contribution of Project Management Practices to Project Success</t>
</si>
<si>
<t>MBTI Personality Types of Project Managers and Their Success: A Field Survey</t>
</si>
<si>
<t>Cohen, Yuval; Ornoy, Hana; Keren, Baruch</t>
</si>
<si>
<t>Development of a Project Management Model for a Government Research and Development Organization</t>
</si>
<si>
<t>Procca, Andrew E.</t>
</si>
<si>
<t>Project Management for Development in Africa: Why Projects are Failing and What Can be Done about It</t>
</si>
<si>
<t>Ika, Lavagnon A.</t>
</si>
<si>
<t>An Empirical Investigation of the Sponsor's Role in Project Initiation</t>
</si>
<si>
<t>Kloppenborg, Timothy J.; Tesch, Deborah; Manolis, Chris; Heitkamp, Mark</t>
</si>
<si>
<t>Applying the Slevin-Pinto Project Implementation Profile to an Information Systems Project</t>
</si>
<si>
<t>Finch, Peter</t>
</si>
<si>
<t>Influence of Communication on Client Satisfaction in Information System Projects: A Quantitative Field Study</t>
</si>
<si>
<t>Diegmann, Phil; Basten, Dirk; Pankratz, Oleg</t>
</si>
<si>
<t>The Successful Delivery of Megaprojects: A Novel Research Method</t>
</si>
<si>
<t>Locatelli, Giorgio; Mikic, Miljan; Kovacevic, Milos; Brookes, Naomi; Ivanisevic, Nenad</t>
</si>
<si>
<t>Managerial Complexity in Process Industrial R&amp;D Projects: A Swedish Study</t>
</si>
<si>
<t>Chronéer, Diana; Bergquist, Bjarne</t>
</si>
<si>
<t>An Empirical Assessment of IT Project Selection and Evaluation Methods in State Government</t>
</si>
<si>
<t>Rosacker, Kirsten M.; Olson, David L.</t>
</si>
<si>
<t>Exploring Research in Project Management: Nine Schools of Project Management Research (Part 4)</t>
</si>
<si>
<t>Bredillet, Christophe N.</t>
</si>
<si>
<t>Using a Social Capital Lens to Identify the Mechanisms of Top Management Commitment: A Case Study of a Technology Project</t>
</si>
<si>
<t>Amoako-Gyampah, Kwasi; Meredith, Jack; Loyd, Kathy White</t>
</si>
<si>
<t>Success of Projects in Different Organizational Conditions</t>
</si>
<si>
<t>Hyväri, Irja</t>
</si>
<si>
<t>Project Control: Literature Review</t>
</si>
<si>
<t>Project Management Research—The Challenge and Opportunity</t>
</si>
<si>
<t>Shenhar, Aaron J.; Dvir, Dov</t>
</si>
<si>
<t>Lessons for IT Project Manager Efficacy: A Review of the Literature Associated with Project Success</t>
</si>
<si>
<t>Millhollan, Chuck; Kaarst-Brown, Michelle</t>
</si>
<si>
<t>Early Warning Signals for R&amp;D Projects: An Empirical Study</t>
</si>
<si>
<t>Sánchez, Angel Martínez; Pérez, Manuela Pérez</t>
</si>
<si>
<t>The Importance of Building a Foundation for User Involvement in Information System Projects</t>
</si>
<si>
<t>Jiang, James J.; Chen, Edward; Klein, Gary</t>
</si>
<si>
<t>Managing Geographically Distributed Clients throughout the Project Management Life Cycle</t>
</si>
<si>
<t>Javed, Talha; Manzil-E-Maqsood; Durrani, Qaiser S.</t>
</si>
<si>
<t>Project Management in the Information Systems and Information Technologies Industries</t>
</si>
<si>
<t>Hartman, Francis; Ashrafi, Rafi A.</t>
</si>
<si>
<t>Project Success: A Cultural Framework</t>
</si>
<si>
<t>Kendra, Korin; Taplin, Laura J.</t>
</si>
<si>
<t>Impact of Organizational and Project Factors on Acceptance and Usage of Project Management Software and Perceived Project Success</t>
</si>
<si>
<t>Bani Ali, Abdullah Saeed; Anbari, Frank T.; Money, William H.</t>
</si>
<si>
<t>Critical Success Factors Affecting Project Performance: An Analysis of Tools, Practices, and Managerial Support</t>
</si>
<si>
<t>Jitpaiboon, Thawatchai; Smith, Sheila M.; Gu, Qiannong</t>
</si>
<si>
<t>Legislative Body</t>
</si>
<si>
<t>History</t>
</si>
<si>
<t>Committee</t>
</si>
<si>
<t>Session</t>
</si>
<si>
<t>Section</t>
</si>
<si>
<t>Code Number</t>
</si>
<si>
<t>Code</t>
</si>
<si>
<t>System</t>
</si>
<si>
<t>Version</t>
</si>
<si>
<t>Programming Language</t>
</si>
<si>
<t>Priority Numbers</t>
</si>
<si>
<t>Legal Status</t>
</si>
<si>
<t>Reporter</t>
</si>
<si>
<t>References</t>
</si>
<si>
<t>Court</t>
</si>
<si>
<t>Conference Name</t>
</si>
<si>
<t>Meeting Name</t>
</si>
<si>
<t>Country</t>
</si>
<si>
<t>Issuing Authority</t>
</si>
<si>
<t>Assignee</t>
</si>
<si>
<t>Application Number</t>
</si>
<si>
<t>Filing Date</t>
</si>
<si>
<t>Artwork Size</t>
</si>
<si>
<t>Medium</t>
</si>
<si>
<t>Scale</t>
</si>
<si>
<t>Running Time</t>
</si>
<si>
<t>Otsikko</t>
</si>
<si>
<t>Arvio</t>
</si>
<si>
<t>Vuosi</t>
</si>
<si>
<t>Julkaisu</t>
</si>
<si>
<t>Tekijä(t)</t>
</si>
<si>
<t>Viittauksia (Semantic Scholar)</t>
</si>
<si>
<t>Stankovic, Dragan; Nikolic, Vesna; Djordjevic, Miodrag; Cao, Dac-Buu</t>
</si>
<si>
<t>A survey study of critical success factors in agile software projects in former Yugoslavia IT companies</t>
</si>
<si>
<t>Journal of Systems and Software</t>
</si>
<si>
<t>Chow, Tsun; Cao, Dac-Buu</t>
</si>
<si>
<t>A survey study of critical success factors in agile software projects</t>
</si>
<si>
<t>Parolia, Neeraj; Jiang, James J.; Klein, Gary</t>
</si>
<si>
<t>The presence and development of competency in IT programs</t>
</si>
<si>
<t>Egorova, Evgenia; Torchiano, Marco; Morisio, Maurizio</t>
</si>
<si>
<t>Actual vs. perceived effect of software engineering practices in the Italian industry</t>
</si>
<si>
<t>Rola, Pawe&amp;#322;; Kuchta, Dorota; Kopczyk, Dominika</t>
</si>
<si>
<t>Conceptual model of working space for Agile (Scrum) project team</t>
</si>
<si>
<t>Verner, J. M.; Babar, M. A.; Cerpa, N.; Hall, T.; Beecham, S.</t>
</si>
<si>
<t>Factors that motivate software engineering teams: A four country empirical study</t>
</si>
<si>
<t>Linberg, Kurt R</t>
</si>
<si>
<t>Software developer perceptions about software project failure: a case study</t>
</si>
<si>
<t>Fontana, Rafaela Mantovani; Meyer, Victor; Reinehr, Sheila; Malucelli, Andreia</t>
</si>
<si>
<t>Progressive Outcomes: A framework for maturing in agile software development</t>
</si>
<si>
<t>Bauer, Veronika; Vetro', Antonio</t>
</si>
<si>
<t>Comparing reuse practices in two large software-producing companies</t>
</si>
<si>
<t>Gottschalk, Petter; Terje Karlsen, Jan</t>
</si>
<si>
<t>A comparison of leadership roles in internal IT projects versus outsourcing projects</t>
</si>
<si>
<t>Industrial Management &amp; Data Systems</t>
</si>
<si>
<t>Nemati, Hamid R.; Barko, Christopher D.</t>
</si>
<si>
<t>Key factors for achieving organizational data&amp;#8208;mining success</t>
</si>
<si>
<t>Czuchry, Andrew J.; Yasin, Mahmoud M.</t>
</si>
<si>
<t>Managing the project management process</t>
</si>
<si>
<t>Balachandra, R.</t>
</si>
<si>
<t>An expert system for new product development projects</t>
</si>
<si>
<t>Holst, Lars; Bolmsjö, Gunnar</t>
</si>
<si>
<t>Simulation integration in manufacturing system development: a study of Japanese industry</t>
</si>
<si>
<t>Ojiako, Udechukwu; Johansen, Eric; Greenwood, David</t>
</si>
<si>
<t>A qualitative re&amp;#8208;construction of project measurement criteria</t>
</si>
<si>
<t>Spalek, Seweryn</t>
</si>
<si>
<t>Does investment in project management pay off?</t>
</si>
<si>
<t>Tsoy, Mikhail; Staples, D. Sandy</t>
</si>
<si>
<t>What Are the Critical Success Factors for Agile Analytics Projects?</t>
</si>
<si>
<t>Information Systems Management</t>
</si>
<si>
<t>Gingnell, Liv; Franke, Ulrik; Lagerström, Robert; Ericsson, Evelina; Lilliesköld, Joakim</t>
</si>
<si>
<t>Quantifying Success Factors for IT Projects—An Expert-Based Bayesian Model</t>
</si>
<si>
<t>Kanter, Jerome; Walsh, John J.</t>
</si>
<si>
<t>Toward More Successful Project Management</t>
</si>
<si>
<t>Readers, Dear</t>
</si>
<si>
<t>From the Editor</t>
</si>
<si>
<t>Lech, Przemys&amp;#322;aw</t>
</si>
<si>
<t>Time, Budget, And Functionality?—IT Project Success Criteria Revised</t>
</si>
<si>
<t>Aranyossy, Márta; Blaskovics, Bálint; Horváth, Ákos Ardzsuna</t>
</si>
<si>
<t>How universal are IT project success and failure factors? Evidence from Hungary</t>
</si>
<si>
<t>Purna Sudhakar, Goparaju</t>
</si>
<si>
<t>A model of critical success factors for software projects</t>
</si>
<si>
<t>Journal of Enterprise Information Management</t>
</si>
<si>
<t>Kuruppuarachchi, Palitha R.; Mandal, Purnendu; Smith, Ross</t>
</si>
<si>
<t>IT project implementation strategies for effective changes: a critical review</t>
</si>
<si>
<t>Logistics Information Management</t>
</si>
<si>
<t>Mangla, Sachin K.; Raut, Rakesh; Narwane, Vaibhav S.; Zhang, Zuopeng (Justin); priyadarshinee, Pragati</t>
</si>
<si>
<t>Mediating effect of big data analytics on project performance of small and medium enterprises</t>
</si>
<si>
<t>Wang, Jian-Jun; Sasanipoor, Negin; Wang, Meng-Meng</t>
</si>
<si>
<t>The influence of PRINCE2 standard on customer satisfaction in information technology outsourcing: an investigation of a mediated moderation model</t>
</si>
<si>
<t>Kazancoglu, Yigit; Ozbiltekin Pala, Melisa; Sezer, Muruvvet Deniz; Luthra, Sunil; Kumar, Anil</t>
</si>
<si>
<t>Drivers of implementing Big Data Analytics in food supply chains for transition to a circular economy and sustainable operations management</t>
</si>
<si>
<t>Karlsen, Jan Terje; Gottschalk, Petter</t>
</si>
<si>
<t>An Empirical Evaluation of Knowledge Transfer Mechanisms for it Projects</t>
</si>
<si>
<t>Journal of Computer Information Systems</t>
</si>
<si>
<t>Conca, Christopher</t>
</si>
<si>
<t>Capturing and Comparing Objectively and Subjectively Determined Decision Models in User Information Satisfaction Judgment Formation</t>
</si>
<si>
<t>Oh, Junyoung; Lee, Hwansoo; Zo, Hangjung</t>
</si>
<si>
<t>The Effect of Leadership and Teamwork on ISD Project Success</t>
</si>
<si>
<t>Money, William H.; Kaisler, Stephen H.; Cohen, Stephen J.</t>
</si>
<si>
<t>Understanding Failed Software Projects through Forensic Analysis</t>
</si>
<si>
<t>Sarker, Saonee; Munson, Charles L; Sarker, Suprateek; Chakraborty, Suranjan</t>
</si>
<si>
<t>Assessing the relative contribution of the facets of agility to distributed systems development success: an Analytic Hierarchy Process approach</t>
</si>
<si>
<t>European Journal of Information Systems</t>
</si>
<si>
<t>Mesgari, Mostafa; Okoli, Chitu</t>
</si>
<si>
<t>Critical review of organisation-technology sensemaking: towards technology materiality, discovery, and action</t>
</si>
<si>
<t>Buchanan, Steven; McMenemy, David</t>
</si>
<si>
<t>Digital service analysis and design: The role of process modelling</t>
</si>
<si>
<t>International Journal of Information Management</t>
</si>
<si>
<t>Kamble, Sachin S.; Gunasekaran, Angappa; Sharma, Rohit</t>
</si>
<si>
<t>Modeling the blockchain enabled traceability in agriculture supply chain</t>
</si>
<si>
<t>Jinasena, Dakshitha N.; Spanaki, Konstantina; Papadopoulos, Thanos; Balta, Maria E.</t>
</si>
<si>
<t>Success and Failure Retrospectives of FinTech Projects: A Case Study Approach</t>
</si>
<si>
<t>Information Systems Frontiers</t>
</si>
<si>
<t>Gill, Asif Qumer; Henderson-Sellers, Brian; Niazi, Mahmood</t>
</si>
<si>
<t>Scaling for agility: A reference model for hybrid traditional-agile software development methodologies</t>
</si>
<si>
<t>Fr&amp;#261;czkowski, Kazimierz; G&amp;#322;adysz, Barbara; Kuchta, Dorota; Stanek, Stanis&amp;#322;aw</t>
</si>
<si>
<t>Selection of IT projects to be implemented in an organisation to maximise their success probability</t>
</si>
<si>
<t>Journal of Decision Systems</t>
</si>
<si>
<t>Marchwicka, Ewa</t>
</si>
<si>
<t>A technique for supporting decision process of global software project monitoring and rescheduling based on risk analysis</t>
</si>
<si>
<t>Hidding, Gezinus J.; Nicholas, John M.</t>
</si>
<si>
<t>A new way of thinking about IT project management practices: Early empirical results</t>
</si>
<si>
<t>Journal of Organizational Computing and Electronic Commerce</t>
</si>
<si>
<t>Fleisch, Elgar; Oesterle, Hubert; Powell, Stephen</t>
</si>
<si>
<t>Rapid Implementation of Enterprise Resource Planning Systems</t>
</si>
<si>
<t>Cockcroft, Sophie</t>
</si>
<si>
<t>A media analysis approach to evaluating national health information infrastructure development</t>
</si>
<si>
<t>Journal of Systems and Information Technology</t>
</si>
<si>
<t>Varajão, João; Fernandes, Gabriela; Silva, Hélio</t>
</si>
<si>
<t>Most used project management tools and techniques in information systems projects</t>
</si>
<si>
<t>Dale, Mark; Scheepers, Helana</t>
</si>
<si>
<t>Enterprise architecture implementation as interpersonal connection: Building support and commitment</t>
</si>
<si>
<t>Information Systems Journal</t>
</si>
<si>
<t>Doherty, Neil F; Ashurst, Colin; Peppard, Joe</t>
</si>
<si>
<t>Factors Affecting the Successful Realisation of Benefits from Systems Development Projects: Findings from Three Case Studies</t>
</si>
<si>
<t>Journal of Information Technology</t>
</si>
<si>
<t>Seddon, Peter B.; Calvert, Cheryl; Yang, Song</t>
</si>
<si>
<t>A Multi-Project Model of Key Factors Affecting Organizational Benefits from Enterprise Systems</t>
</si>
<si>
<t>MIS Quarterly</t>
</si>
<si>
<t>Dweiri, F. T.; Kablan, M. M.</t>
</si>
<si>
<t>Using fuzzy decision making for the evaluation of the project management internal efficiency</t>
</si>
<si>
<t>Decision Support Systems</t>
</si>
<si>
<t>Gavidia, Jose V.; Junglas, Iris A.; Chou, Chen-Huei</t>
</si>
<si>
<t>An integrated model of ERP success: the critical role of task-context alignment</t>
</si>
<si>
<t>Enterprise Information Systems</t>
</si>
<si>
<t>Vaidya, Omkarprasad S.; Kumar, Sushil</t>
</si>
<si>
<t>Analytic hierarchy process: An overview of applications</t>
</si>
<si>
<t>European Journal of Operational Research</t>
</si>
<si>
<t>Xu, Xiaobo; Zhang, Weiyong; Barkhi, Reza</t>
</si>
<si>
<t>IT infrastructure capabilities and IT project success: a development team perspective</t>
</si>
<si>
<t>Information Technology and Management</t>
</si>
<si>
<t>Banerjee, Snehasish; Singh, Jyoti Prakash; Dwivedi, Yogesh K.; Rana, Nripendra P.</t>
</si>
<si>
<t>Social media analytics for end-users' expectation management in information systems development projects</t>
</si>
<si>
<t>Information Technology &amp; People</t>
</si>
<si>
<t>Melton, Horace L.; Hartline, Michael D.</t>
</si>
<si>
<t>Customer and Frontline Employee Influence on New Service Development Performance</t>
</si>
<si>
<t>Journal of Service Research</t>
</si>
<si>
<t>Leung, H. M.; Rao Tummala, V. M.; Chuah, K. B.</t>
</si>
<si>
<t>A knowledge-based system for identifying potential project risks</t>
</si>
<si>
<t>Omega</t>
</si>
<si>
<t>Ulhas, Khire Rushikesh; Lai, Jung-Yu; Wang, Juite</t>
</si>
<si>
<t>Impacts of collaborative IS on software development project success in Indian software firms: a service perspective</t>
</si>
<si>
<t>Information Systems and e-Business Management</t>
</si>
<si>
<t>Zarndt, Frederick</t>
</si>
<si>
<t>Project management 101: Plan well, communicate a lot, and don't forget acceptance criteria!</t>
</si>
<si>
<t>OCLC Systems &amp; Services: International digital library perspectives</t>
</si>
<si>
<t>De Marsico, Maria; Kimani, Stephen; Mirabella, Valeria; Norman, Kent L.; Catarci, Tiziana</t>
</si>
<si>
<t>A proposal toward the development of accessible e-learning content by human involvement</t>
</si>
<si>
<t>Universal Access in the Information Society</t>
</si>
<si>
<t>✔</t>
</si>
<si>
<t>❌</t>
</si>
<si>
<t>Huomiot</t>
</si>
<si>
<t>Käsittelee ehkä enemmän projektipäällikköä ja konteksti on väärä (defense)</t>
</si>
<si>
<t>Osuva, muttei käsittele ohjelmistoprojekteja (geneerinen)</t>
</si>
<si>
<t>Konteksti väärä, keskittyy liikaa henkilöihin</t>
</si>
<si>
<t>Konteksti väärä, menestystekijät mainitaan vaan kerran</t>
</si>
<si>
<t>Konteksti väärä, aihe väärä</t>
</si>
<si>
<t>2. Konteksti hyvä, vain yksi maininta menestystekijöistä</t>
</si>
<si>
<t>2. Konteksti hyvä, aihe ok (vain yksi menestystekijä, johtajuus, kritiikkinä muutta aiheen tutkimusta kohtaan)</t>
</si>
<si>
<t>2. Hyvää tekstiä onnistumisen määrittelyn vaikeudesta</t>
</si>
<si>
<t>1. Konteksti oikea, aihe relevantti, käsittelee menestystekijöitä (Taulukko)</t>
</si>
<si>
<t>2. Ei 100 % relevantti, mutta kirjoittajat todistettavasti tietoisia ohjelmistoprojektien erityispiirteistä</t>
</si>
<si>
<t>1. Konteksi nappiin, käsittelee ohjelmistokehitystä, mutta käsittelee lisäksi myös supplier/customer sekä failure perspektiivejä</t>
</si>
<si>
<t>1. Konteksti nappiin, mutta käsittelee projektien menestymistä ja menestystekijät on siinä vain sivussa apuna.</t>
</si>
<si>
<t>1. Nappiin</t>
</si>
<si>
<t>1. Todella hyvä.</t>
</si>
<si>
<t>Konteksti väärä (manufacturing)</t>
</si>
<si>
<t>Frączkowski, Kazimierz; Gładysz, Barbara; Kuchta, Dorota; Stanek, Stanisław</t>
</si>
<si>
<t>Ei helppoa pääsyä JYKDOK:ista ja otsikon perusteella aihe menee ohi</t>
</si>
<si>
<t>+2 (Chaos Report 2015 ja Chaos Reporttien kritiikki)</t>
</si>
<si>
<t>Aihe jälleen ehkä vähän ohi, mutta konteksti 1/3 oikein</t>
</si>
<si>
<t>2. Aihe menee ehkä vähän ohi, mutta viittaa Bahli and Rivard 2005 (tutkimus joka käsittelee menestystekijöitä?, backwards snowballing)</t>
</si>
<si>
<t>1. Kritiikkiä, hyvä</t>
</si>
<si>
<t>2. Hyvä, aihe sivuaa vähän, mutta kritiikillä perustellen</t>
</si>
<si>
<t>2. Esimerkki siitä, kuinka menestystekijöiden tutkimusta on voitu hyödyntää ja valitsee jollakin perustella aikaisemmasta kirjallisuudesta menestystekijöitä</t>
</si>
<si>
<t>2. Mahdollista kriittikiä yleisiin linjoihin tutkimuksessa. Konteksti hyvä ja aihe hyvä.</t>
</si>
<si>
<t>2. Jaottelua aiheesta</t>
</si>
<si>
<t>1. Konteksti ja aihe hyvä: plussaa erilainen lähestymistapa mutta ilmeisesti vain päätyy samoihin lopputuloksiin</t>
</si>
<si>
<t>2. Konteksti hyvä, käyttää aihetta ehkä enemmän tarkastelun välineenä kuin tutkii sitä. Ehkä hyvää pohdintaa saa tästä irti</t>
</si>
<si>
<t>2. Käsittelee yhtä menestystekijää, mutta aika laajasti. Konteksti oikein.</t>
</si>
<si>
<t>2. Konteksti rajoittuu Intiaan, mutta puhuu kuitenkin semi-yleisesti menestystekijöistä</t>
</si>
<si>
<t>2. Aihe ok, konteksti semi oikein (fintech)</t>
</si>
<si>
<t>1. Hyvä</t>
</si>
<si>
<t>1. Hyvä, mutta vanha</t>
</si>
<si>
<t>2. Hyvä, mutta konteksti ehkä turhan spesifi</t>
</si>
<si>
<t>3. Hyvä, mutta tosi spesifi</t>
</si>
<si>
<t>3. Tosi spesifi (leadership)</t>
</si>
<si>
<t>3. Käsittelee riskien kautta</t>
</si>
<si>
<t>1. Hyvä, IS</t>
</si>
<si>
<t>2. Hyvä, mutta kontekstina stakeholderit</t>
</si>
<si>
<t>2. Hyvä, mutta joku johtajuusjuttu</t>
</si>
<si>
<t>3. Puhuu epäonnistumisesta, mutta taustalla menestystekijät</t>
</si>
<si>
<t>Toimii kritiikkinä 2008 artikkelille</t>
</si>
<si>
<t>2. Hyvä, mutta konteksti aika laaja</t>
</si>
<si>
<t>1. Hyvä (vanha)</t>
</si>
<si>
<t>Konteksti väärä</t>
</si>
<si>
<t>Konteksti osittain oikein, muttei käsittele tarpeeksi menestystekijöitä</t>
</si>
<si>
<t>Ei puhu tarpeeksi ohjelmistoista</t>
</si>
<si>
<t>1. Ok, plus viittaa ehkä johonkin mielenkiintoiseen</t>
</si>
<si>
<t>Viittauksia per vuosi</t>
</si>
<si>
<t>Poistunut kansainvälisistä e-aineistoista 14.01.2022</t>
</si>
<si>
<t>2. Toimii kritiikkinä 2008 artikkelille</t>
</si>
<si>
<t>Kiinnitetään mukaan?</t>
</si>
<si>
<t>⚫</t>
</si>
<si>
<t>Lisähuomioita</t>
</si>
<si>
<t>Ohjelmistoala mainitaan vain ohimennen. Käyttää lyhennettä PSF (Project Success Factor)</t>
</si>
<si>
<t>Täältä saa hyvää pohdintaa irti siitä, mitä menestystekijät ovat, viittauksilla</t>
</si>
<si>
<t>Hyvää pohdintaa "lonely" projektit</t>
</si>
<si>
<t>Ohjaa kirjaan (Marchewka, 2010), mutta ei lainattavissa joten siihen tullaan viittaamaan tämän lähteen kautta</t>
</si>
<si>
<t>Voi olla turhan tilastotieteellinen/matemaattinen</t>
</si>
<si>
<t>Viittaa myös useaan muuhun lähteeseen</t>
</si>
<si>
<t>Lumipallo</t>
</si>
<si>
<t>Hyvää pohdintaa menestystekijöiden universaalisuudesta</t>
</si>
<si>
<t>Valitsi vain kaksi menestystekijää muusta kirjallisuudesta</t>
</si>
<si>
<t>Keskittyy tiimiin eikä projektiin</t>
</si>
<si>
<t>Hyvää pohdintaa menestystekijätutkimusten tuloksista</t>
</si>
<si>
<t>Viittaa Chow et al 2008, mahdollisesti tukien sitä vs. toinen lähde joka kritisoi sitä</t>
</si>
<si>
<t>Vaihtoehtoinen lähestymistapa</t>
</si>
<si>
<t>Hyvää pohdintaa</t>
</si>
<si>
<t>Keskittyy liikaa johtajuuteen</t>
</si>
<si>
<t>Previous work otsikon alla hyvää pohdintaa, mutta menestystekijöiden käsittely muuten aika suppeaa</t>
</si>
<si>
<t>Menestystekijöiden käsittely turhan suppeaa</t>
</si>
<si>
<t>PDF rikki</t>
</si>
<si>
<t>Information Systems Project Success Factors: Literature Review</t>
</si>
<si>
<t>Viittaa omaan 2020 tutkimukseen</t>
</si>
<si>
<t>Outo julkaisu (artikkelia ei löydy jykdokilla, JUFO ei tunne julkaisua) ja vain kaksi viittausta joista toinen tutkijan oma</t>
</si>
<si>
<t>Viittaa Chow et al 2008, kritisoiden sitä</t>
</si>
<si>
<t>Kaksi muuta artikkelia viittaa tähän</t>
</si>
<si>
<t>Validating measures of information technology outsourcing risk factors</t>
</si>
<si>
<t>Bahli et al ei käsittele menestystekijöitä riittävästi</t>
</si>
<si>
<t>Ei käsittele menestystekijöitä riittävästi</t>
</si>
<si>
<t>Bouchaib Bahli, Suzanne Rivard</t>
</si>
<si>
<t>Analysis of Critical Success Factors in IT Project Management</t>
</si>
<si>
<t>Ei vertaisarvioitu?</t>
</si>
<si>
<t>International Conference on Industrial and Information Systems</t>
</si>
<si>
<t>LUE TÄMÄ KOKONAAN (ei päällekkäisyyttä lähteissä)</t>
</si>
<si>
<t>Critical Success Factors In Software Projects</t>
</si>
<si>
<t>IEEE Software</t>
</si>
<si>
<t>Reel, John</t>
</si>
<si>
<t>What do software practitioners really think about project success: A cross-cultural comparison</t>
</si>
<si>
<t>The Journal of Systems and Software</t>
</si>
<si>
<t>Javier Pereira</t>
</si>
<si>
<t>Tuo hyvää lisäapua Chow + myöhempi Yugoslavia vertailuun (myös Ulhas 2016)</t>
</si>
<si>
<t>Fan</t>
</si>
<si>
<t>Ohjaa toiseen lähteeseen (Fan, 2010), jota ei ole vertaisarvioitu</t>
</si>
<si>
<t>Suppeahko, mutta puhuu muusta tutkimuksesta ja tulokset ilmeisesti linjassa toistensa kanssa</t>
</si>
<si>
<t>Iron triangle taitaa esiintyä myös muualla</t>
</si>
<si>
<t>Hyvää jaottelua menestystekijöistä</t>
</si>
<si>
<t>ja +2 Chaos report 2015 sekä sen kritiikki (kritiikki tieteellinen, chaos report muuten vain keskeinen)</t>
</si>
<si>
<t>Ei järkeä viitata, sillä sisältyy jo osaksi Purnan (2012) tutkimusta. - toki tämän avulla voisi maalata historiaa mutta nyt lukemisen aikana tämä tutkimus alkaa aiheuttaa mulle pahoinvointia</t>
</si>
<si>
<t>Luvussa 2.2. hyvää läpikäyntiä</t>
</si>
<si>
<t>kritiikki ei ehkä olennainen mutta auttaa mua kontekstualisoimaan asioita</t>
</si>
<si>
<t>Konteksti ehkä turhan spesifi + ei riitä aika lukea</t>
</si>
<si>
<t>Hylätään, aika vähän viittauksia. Vanha: Ohjaa pereira et al What do software practitioners really think about project success: a cross-cultural comparison. Se ohjaa case study: factors jne., joka on jo hylätty koska se on rikkinäinen pdf. Lisäksi sen pdf:n viitteet muualle ovat jo aika vanhoja</t>
</si>
<si>
<t>Hylätään: Software vain murto-osa kontekstista, mutta tuo tiettyä yleistettävyyttä</t>
</si>
<si>
<t>Ei käsittele ohjelmistoalaa tarpeeksi ekplisiittisesti</t>
</si>
</sst>
