<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?>
<sst xmlns="http://schemas.openxmlformats.org/spreadsheetml/2006/main" count="293" uniqueCount="66">
<si>
<t>A model of critical success factors for software projects</t>
</si>
<si>
<t>A new way of thinking about IT project management practices Early empirical results</t>
</si>
<si>
<t>A study of the impact of project classification on project risk indicators</t>
</si>
<si>
<t>A survey on the characteristics of projects with success in delivering client benefits</t>
</si>
<si>
<t>A survey study of critical success factors in agile software projects in former Yugoslavia IT companies</t>
</si>
<si>
<t>A survey study of critical success factors in agile software projects</t>
</si>
<si>
<t>CHAOS REPORT 2015</t>
</si>
<si>
<t>Evaluating logistic regression models to estimate software project outcomes</t>
</si>
<si>
<t>Factors Affecting the Successful Realisation of Benefits from Systems Development Projects Findings from Three Case Studies</t>
</si>
<si>
<t>How Can Agile Methodologies Be Used to Enhance the Success of Information Technology Projects</t>
</si>
<si>
<t>How universal are IT project success and failure factors Evidence from Hungary</t>
</si>
<si>
<t>Lessons for IT Project Manager Efficacy A Review of the Literature Associated with Project Success</t>
</si>
<si>
<t>Project Success A Cultural Framework</t>
</si>
<si>
<t>Quantifying Success Factors for IT Projects—An Expert-Based Bayesian Model</t>
</si>
<si>
<t>Software development project success and failure from the supplier's perspective A systematic literature review</t>
</si>
<si>
<t>Standardized project management may increase development projects success</t>
</si>
<si>
<t>The influence of business managers' IT competence on IT project success</t>
</si>
<si>
<t>The Rise and Fall of the Chaos Report Figures</t>
</si>
<si>
<t>Time, Budget, And Functionality—IT Project Success Criteria Revised</t>
</si>
<si>
<t>What Are the Critical Success Factors for Agile Analytics Projects</t>
</si>
<si>
<t>What do software practitioners really think about project success A cross-cultural comparison</t>
</si>
<si>
<t>Artikkeli</t>
</si>
<si>
<t>X</t>
</si>
<si>
<t>-</t>
</si>
<si>
<t>?</t>
</si>
<si>
<t>Project and PM</t>
</si>
<si>
<t>Product and PM</t>
</si>
<si>
<t>Kolmijako</t>
</si>
<si>
<t>Sisäinen viite</t>
</si>
<si>
<t>Sudhakar (2012)</t>
</si>
<si>
<t>Hidding ja Nicholas (2017)</t>
</si>
<si>
<t>Yim ym. (2015)</t>
</si>
<si>
<t>Jørgensen (2016)</t>
</si>
<si>
<t>Stankovic ym. (2013)</t>
</si>
<si>
<t>Chow ja Cao (2008)</t>
</si>
<si>
<t>Standish Group (2015)</t>
</si>
<si>
<t>Cerpa ym. (2010)</t>
</si>
<si>
<t>Doherty ym. (2012)</t>
</si>
<si>
<t>Truong ja Jitbaipoon (2016)</t>
</si>
<si>
<t>Millhollan ja Kaarst-Brown (2018)</t>
</si>
<si>
<t>Kendra ja Taplin (2004)</t>
</si>
<si>
<t>Gingnell ym. (2014)</t>
</si>
<si>
<t>Savolainen ym. (2012)</t>
</si>
<si>
<t>Milosevic ja Patanakul (2005)</t>
</si>
<si>
<t>Engelbrecht ym. (2017)</t>
</si>
<si>
<t>Eveleens ja Verhoef (2010)</t>
</si>
<si>
<t>Lech (2013)</t>
</si>
<si>
<t>Tsoy ja Staples (2021)</t>
</si>
<si>
<t>Pereira ym. (2008)</t>
</si>
<si>
<t>Chaos report</t>
</si>
<si>
<t>CR kritiikki</t>
</si>
<si>
<t>Ei mainintaa</t>
</si>
<si>
<t>Product</t>
</si>
<si>
<t>Project</t>
</si>
<si>
<t>money</t>
</si>
<si>
<t>PMBOK</t>
</si>
<si>
<t>triangle</t>
</si>
<si>
<t>triple</t>
</si>
<si>
<t>2 edellistä</t>
</si>
<si>
<t>x</t>
</si>
<si>
<t>Stakehold</t>
</si>
<si>
<t>SH mittarina</t>
</si>
<si>
<t>Liian pieni aineisto</t>
</si>
<si>
<t>Ero keskiarvoon pieni, tukee toisaalta omaa pointtia paremmin. Lisäksi nyt ilmoitettu vuosi on varmemmin lähempänä jotain oikeasti julkaistua artikkelia. Voidaan vaihtaa tähän.</t>
</si>
<si>
<t>Aranyossy, Blaskovics ja Horváth (2018)</t>
</si>
<si>
<t>Päivitetyt (Zoteron vuodet):</t>
</si>
</sst>
